Ezequiel Joaquín Zion

I'm a Fullstack Engineer based in Buenos Aires, Argentina 🚬

I have always strived to understand the *hows* and the *whys* great things are **great**, so that I can implement it in what I produce.

I have a strong passion for design and UX, and intend to make it my field of expertise.

- ▼ >> Let's keep in touch
 - +54 9 11 3323 4385
 - 🔀 Email
 - **Github**

Professional Experience:

Fullstack Developer

PSh | Jan. 2021 - Present

- Full time
- · Helping produce top-notch functionalities for a US client
- Using React, CSS, TypeScript, Node.js, Redux, PostgreSQL, etc.
- Developing function components from scratch with a keen eye to detail and great UX
- Code reviewing my peers and helping them with debugging and to provide solutions
- Implementing unit and integration tests using Jest
- Working with agile methodologies, with 3-week sprints and daily direct meetings with the client and their team

Website Management

Country Magazine | May 2020 - December 2020

- Freelance
- Successfully migrated their website from Joomla to Wordpress
- In charge of designing the look and feel of the site
- Helped restructure how content was presented
- Used HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL, FileZilla, cPanel, etc.

Skills & Knowledge:

- HTML
- CSS
 - Styled Components
- Javascript
 - React
 - Node.js
 - TypeScript
 - Next.js
 - Jest
- Redux
- PostgreSQL
- Git
- Linux

Education:

Universidad de Buenos Aires

Computer Science Degree | 2019 - Present

Escuela Técnica ORT

Programming & Digital Media Specialization | 2013 - 2017

Languages:

- Spanish (native)
- English (C1 CEER Level)
- Italian (A2 CEFR Level)
- Portuguese

Acknowledgements:

• Was <u>awarded</u> by World ORT in the STEM Communication Awards 2017

You can also check the <u>online version</u> of this resume, which is always up to date

Ezequiel Joaquín Zion 1